Charl-Pierre Marais

Computer Science Student at Utrecht University



Personal details



Charl-Pierre Marais



charlpierre0301@gmail.com



06-50653747



Baudevoort 29 5706 KL Helmond



January 3, 2002



License B



C#

linkedin.com/in/charl-pierre-marais-204744220

Skills

Git	••••
Python	••••
TypeScript/HTML/CSS	••••
SQL	••••
Haskell	••••
C++	••••
Software Testing	••••
Computer Animation / Image Editing	••••

Profile

I'm Charlie, a resourceful and curious Computer Science student with a love for programming and making games. Being born in South-Africa, then moving to the UK only to grow up in the Netherlands has given me a broad range of experiences that I use to improve myself and continually grow my skill set.

Education

Master's degree, Game and Media Technology Aug 2023

Utrecht University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Sep 2020 - Aug 2023

Utrecht University

VWO, Natuur en Techniek

2014 - 2020

Jan van Brabant College

Employment

Teaching Assistant

Nov 2023

Utrecht University, Utrecht, Utrecht, Netherlands \cdot Hybrid Courses:

- Software Testing & Verification
- Persuasive Technologies

Assembly Line Worker

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

Spirotech BV, Helmond, North Brabant, Netherlands

Assembly Line Worker

Jun 2019 - Jul 2019

Spirotech BV, Helmond, North Brabant, Netherlands

Game Programmer

Mar 2019 - Mar 2019

BeamNG GmbH, Bremen, Germany

Assembly Line Worker

Jun 2018 - Jul 2018

Spirotech BV, Helmond, North Brabant, Netherlands

Certificates

Diploma of Education, English Language and Literature, Higher Level

International Baccalaureate

Goethe-Zertifikat B1

Aug 2020

Apr 2018

Languages

English	••••
Dutch	••••
Afrikaans	••••
German	••••
French	••••